

# Maxim Sheshukov

Berlin, Germany



+4915256004078



sheshukovmaxim@gmail.com



go-maxus-go

A results-oriented software engineer with more than 7 years of work experience. Well-versed in producing efficient, reusable and readable code. Initiative and creative, constantly looking for ways for improvement. Some of my personal projects are Foody (Flutter), Marbles Puzzle (Qt, QML), di (C++).

# Work experience

Software Engineer C++ 06/2019 - nowadays

Lead Software Engineer C++/Qt 11/2018 - 03/2019

**Software Engineer C++** 01/2018 - 11/2018

Software Engineer C++/Qt 10/2017 - 12/2017

**Software Engineer C++/Qt** 

03/2016 - 10/2017

**Software Engineer C++** 

11/2013 - 03/2016

BinarySpaces, Berlin, Germany

- Reduced project save time by 50% by implementing data cache in RAM.
- Implemented a release MVP feature Rotary Table for machine setup.

Escape Technology, Moscow, Russia

Moving avatars like in Telegram .

Luxoft, Moscow, Russia

Added a debugger for Lua scripts.

2GIS, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Implemented the algorithm for choosing the fastest server.

Movavi, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Implemented a Slideshow Maker that became a successful product.

SoftLab-NSK, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Designed a no bullets biathlon training system for children.

### **Education**

**Computer science / Physics** master's degree

09/2006 - 06/2012

Novosibirsk State University, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Section of automation of physical and technical research. Department of physics.

#### Skills

Coding C++, STL, Qt, QML Dart, Flutter

**Boost** 

**Development** Git, CI, CD

OOP, SOLID, TDD

Algorithms, patterns

Languages Russian

**English** 

German



### **Hobbies**



Programming





Traveling



Reading



Computer Games

Strengths

**Critical thinking Quick learning** 

**Teamwork** 

Reliability

**Initiative** 

Leadership